Narrator: 1
A: Right, just leaving home now.
B: Oh great. What’s your ETA?
A: Around 6, 6.30 I’d say.
B: See you then.
Narrator: 2
A: Excuse me, you haven’t seen Mr Knightley’s PA anywhere, have you?
B: Sorry, he seems to have gone AWOL. I haven’t seen him since early this morning.
Narrator: 3
A: What happened to that report you were going to finish?
B: OMG, I completely forgot about it! Sorry, I’ll do it ASAP.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: HIV continues to be a major global public health issue,
especially in East and Southern Africa.
Since the start of the epidemic, an estimated 88.4 million people have become infected
with the virus, and 42.3 million have died of AIDS-related illnesses.
Narrator: 5
A: What do you think of your local MP?
B: Well, I didn’t vote for her, but she’s OK I suppose.
She’s well qualified, she has a degree in law and an MBA, but I don’t really agree with her politics.